Can I have you come back?
戻ってもらっていいですか?
No, what about this?
いや、こうしたいっか?
I can't wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってませんな
Do you slip when drinking?
飲んでたりとすべる?
It's good to start drinking from next month.
来月から飲むのもいいです
Get tested for sexually transmitted diseases.
性病検査して
I can't make mustard right now.
今まなからしができない
Oh no, it's falling.
いやー落ちるね
fall
落ち
Ru.
る
Take your hands and your feet.
手 とり足とり
Make it a bilateral head.
二辺頭にして
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
Oh, really?
えっ、そう?
good.
よかった
I thought it didn't hurt.
痛くなかったかなと思って
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかったですか?
Huh?
えっ、
Don't you want to sleep anymore?
もう 寝たくならん?
Shall we sleep?
寝よか?
Is it okay now?
もうアコいいかな?
Like.
みたいな
I'm waiting for a moment now.
今ちょっと待ってます
It's dazzling.
眩しいですな